

#### CONTACT

Mobile: 4444509521

Email: yberenice.tovarh@gmail.com

Skype: Y. Berenice Tovar

San Luis Potosí, México

#### **ABOUT**

I have experience developing digital projects and business. I love technology that is why I decided to study programming. I am quick learner person, open to feedback and learning. I am familiar with Agile Development and Scrum Project Management.

# **SKILLS**

Negotiation Leadership Communication Teamwork Proactive Problem Solving Organization

## **TECHNOLOGIES**

HTML5
CSS3
Bootstrap
Git / Github
jQuery
WordPress
APls
JavaScript
JSON
ReactJS

# BERENICE TOVAR

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### WORDPRESS PROJECT DEVELOPMENT

Connfi. Dec 2018 - June 2019

- Hosting and Domain configuration.
- WordPress installation.
- Setting up email account with domain name.
- Layout of the web site.
- Installation and management of WooCommerce.
- WooCommerce catalog configuration.
- Plugins installation, including Google Analytics.
- SEO friendly configuration.
- cPanel Administration.

## **BUSINESS CONSULTANT**

Freelance. Sept 2015 - Feb 2018

- Project Management.
- Business plan development.
- Support in the development of e-commerce projects.
- Specialized consultancies.

#### **E-COMMERCE PROJECT MANAGEMENT**

Independent Projects. Jun 2017 - Nov 2017

- Development of two e-commerce stores.
- · Digital Marketing.
- Purchases.
- Contact with international suppliers.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **LABORATORIA**

Front-End Web Developer. March 2018 - September 2018

## UNIVERSIDAD AUTONOMA DE SAN LUIS POTOSI

Bachelor Degree in Commerce and International Business. August 2010 - June 2015

### LANGUAGES

SPANISH Native

**ENGLISH** Advanced